Where are you going?
It's only a matter of time
until her curtain call.
There'll be no encore.
Is he going to hit me with the
Soundmaster's Modified Bloodline Increment?
No, he was just fluffing
so he could run away!
Where is it, if I find it before he does?
This fight's over, and I super win!
Those who ceaselessly hone the art
of killing are known as Masters.
These lethal abilities,
dutifully passed down
through many generations,
have become what are
called modified bloodlines.
This is the story of one such master,
Genya Naruko of the Sound Clan,
and his greatest challenge yet,
the super search for healing.
Mama la la la la I know you
want it I should I love it Da
kāda Kimie no mama la la la la
Run run run Se nacha wasa run
Fun fun fun you so cool Mom buff
Kakeiki no haute de
fukamaru Yamimi o uji nuke
Daigo kakaita mao de
It's strange, I'm behind you!
What do you want to kill or kiss?
Even if the target lives and becomes
CEO, it's not like her troubles will end.
If anything, in fact, she'll
be astronomically worse off.
Her relatives will dissent her.
Human scum will try to tear her down.
Society's rotten to the core.
Her own family will shun her.
She isn't capable of filling those shits.
The competition's going to chew her up.
When the weaklings of the world
are pitted against the strong,
it always ends in tragedy.
She may have room to grow.
might even super work
her butt off but only
strength matters and the weak are destined
for extinction if they venture outside
their comfort zone inevitably they'll break
the super weak are better off living in
nice safe cages where they can't hey naruko
are you that scared by now you should have
a good idea just how
strong ureshino really
is.
Even after you amped up her trauma,
she broke through on her own.
She's conquering her
weakness because she wants to.
Maybe that makes her tougher than
guys like us, who were forced to be
strong.
We share a profession, but we're
on totally different wavelengths.
I finally found it's a super
perfect healing spot fight
inside organic healing compounds
the trees release into the air
the sound master's abilities
aren't made for hand-to-hand
combat to produce music that will
hook my target audience i need
to be in peak condition that's
why the forest is my ideal
battleground these healing compounds
will turn me up to 11 no beyond
even that if i had to keep
this fight inside filled hollow
review it'd be five out of five
stars it's gonna
feel incredible
the super best super bliss i've
ever experienced i control every
sound in this forest I'll bury him
six feet under with a single note!
Modified bloodline plus plus!
Conan!
These aren't fighting signs.
The smell is similar, but
in reality it's poison gas!
He figured out the secrets of my abilities
and used them to lure me into a trap.
But I haven't lost yet!
If I expel the poison first...
Water absorbent polymer!
Soundmaster,
any competent assassin can tell what
you're able to pull off takes great skill.
But stunts as complicated as
yours require specific conditions.
When I use my abilities, it
shaves off a little of my life.
If we're similar, I knew
what you'd need to heal.
My first time mixing a poisonous
gas with fight insides.
It's not exactly the
easiest task in the world,
but laying traps like
this is my specialty.
Poison Master, I've super gotta
thank you for buying into my lies.
Why isn't Kinosaki
picking up taking me down
no luck yet shit won't stop the hysteria?
We're out of options who's
the youngest after Ureishino?
Come on this way I found an old road
west of the village that leads into town.
That's great except change of plans I've
got to go back to the
others are you insane?
No, they won't stop till they kill you.
You need to escape before it's too late.
I won't go.
I'd just be saving myself
Will someone else get
sacrificed in my place?
My classmates for the rest of their lives.
That's why I
Can't leave but I have an idea
Sorry about this, Osawa.
It's the only way to placate Lord Cladney.
It sucks, but someone's gotta go!
Please wait!
There she is!
Grab her!
It's that time.
Wake, flame devil.
Everyone there's nothing to worry about I
will use my powers and
exercise Lord Cladney.
Remember when you speak relax
your body and project from
your diaphragm if it feels slow
then that's the right pace.
Oh and use this perfume it's
a hit with both men and women.
My without fail go-to brand.
Thanks for all your help.
You didn't have to go along with me.
I'm helping because you can do this.
You've come so far since we met. Really.
But if it doesn't work, run. Okay?
Uh, got it.
That's right.
I can pull this off.
I know I can.
And now... Wait a sec!
How's someone like you going to
exorcise the Great Lord Claidney?
So?
You've been running this whole time!
You were scared of being sacrificed!
Yeah!
You're all bark, no bite!
If you're that strong, you
would have done it sooner!
I bet you want all of us
to die! Liar! You coward!
I waited, because I needed
to let my energy build up.
And now that it has, I've
returned to save you.
If you really can, then
hurry up and exercise!
Do it now!
What if I do? Run away!
I can't mess this up or someone is going
to die and everyone's
lives will be ruined.
Not if I've got anything to
say about it, my dear flame.
Devil, are you ready?
Once you give the signal,
I guess up the actor.
That's right.
It's dead leaves, so it should burn.
I know.
I'm asking a lot of you, but no.
It's a walk in the park.
You've got the toughest job:
selling the illusion and making
them believe magic is real.
Now it's time to burn!
There!
Lord Cladney has passed
on to the next life.
So now that that's done...
How about we build a campfire? Sound good?
Sounds like it worked out perfectly.
I'll be there soon.
I'll beat you, Super 1.
Think again.
You didn't lose because of me.
Ureshi no won by overcoming her weakness.
I see.
What are you waiting for?
Take his life!
The weaker fated to die sooner or later,
and dying at his little brother's
hands is the best he can hope for.
The truth is, I've
never been super strong.
Not even once.
It doesn't make sense to spare my life.
Today's a special occasion.
It's orientation.
If you really want to
heal yourself, Naruko,
a little dose of
vulnerability goes a long way.
Poison Master Hikaru Gero,
that's none of your business.
Mr. Gero!
A campfire?
I've heard the legends before, but
I didn't believe they were real!
Gero!
Bureshi-no says she has a present for you.
I'm not sure if you'll like it or not.
It's a super-sized Pixie Bucks Bix-kit!
You were in a fight to the death and
this is the most damage you've taken?
Kinosaki, you don't get it!
This is a historic event!
The world record for the biggest
DIY candy kit hasn't been
broken in 22 years but this one
just blew it out of the water!
Yeah, whatever.
Good morning, everyone!
You must be hungry.
It's almost time for breakfast.
Man, I had the weirdest dream.
Same here.
Odashina was a real witch
and fought a monster.
More like an omnioji.
No, a spirit medium.
Me?
I'm good at magic tricks, that's all.
It looks like our ride's here.
I can't thank you enough, Mr. Gato.
You saved me and smoothed things over.
It was just a little memory
suppression, nothing fancy.
What are you doing?
Oh, sorry.
I wasn't thinking.
My dad used to pat people's heads, and
it's just something I picked up from him.
You pat his head to your
heart's content, Ureshino.
He needs to learn to take a compliment.
It's okay.
Because of everything you
did, no one had to suffer.
And I got to make some absolutely amazing
memories that'll stay with me forever.
But getting to meet and know you?
I'm gonna treasure that one most of all!
Great, but, you know,
don't forget Kinosaki.
I haven't!
Miss Kinosaki already got her headpats!
We got it out of the way
while you weren't looking.
Thus, I can't accept payment.
I'll super return the full amount.
I'm sure she'll handle it well.
Now for a super dip in a bath.
An emerging refreshed in every way.
Don't give me that crap!
The Soundmaster just walked away!
That's shit!
A good thing you sought
out a superior hitman!
Me and my old partner here
will blow her into paste!
What's wrong no one left in your
corner stay back you want my life
would that be enough Maybe my fortune
just one thing please teach me how
to run a business i want to do work
that takes All the gloom in the
world and makes it disappear like
magic after everything i did you i know
You value the future of the Balzak
company more than your own life.
You worked yourself to death to help
my dad turn it into what it is today.
Ultimately, it's up to you whether
to honor my will or not, sister.
But if you think Shiori has what it takes
as CEO, do me a favor and lend her a hand.
I want this.
Work with me.
Together, we can make this company soar.
Please?
I'm as strict as the devil, and
I'm going to put you through hell.
Also, with their help, we...
Close down a second, Gero!
Why should I?
Just checking.
You did get Ureshino's
contact info, right?
I've only dealt with human garbage before.
It wasn't until I met her and Himekawa
that the truth finally hit me!
Turns out this world of ours isn't
as grimy and bleak as I thought?
Who knew?
Getting married isn't what
Ureshino needs right now.
I'd only get in her way.
After considering how she
would feel, I figured.
This is what's best.
Always be thoughtful of the
other person's feelings.
Good job, pupil.
Too bad it didn't work out.
I thought you two could have hit it off.
Well, on to the next girl.
You can't leave yet.
There's business.
We haven't finished.
Something that I...
No, both of us haven't done that.
We need to let's have a
drinking party a fun one.
What do you say?
Does everyone have something
to drink ready to go?
Yeah, okay, then since we're ready
So, um, did you happen to
catch this week's ropes, Mr.
Gato?
Sorry?
Short for termination to survive, but
they said they're going to win 10-30!
Guess not.
The other day, I rode a real-life
shark. A shark? Are you kidding?
Chomsky, Inosaki, rode him too.
It is as rough as they say.
That's crazy.
They couldn't keep a conversation
going if their lives depended on it.
I already knew that, but still.
Not to mention they're from two
different worlds with nothing in common.
We're playing on hard mode.
They didn't have much
trouble talking on the trip,
but now that it's just
them they're clamming
up at this rate.
A rift will form between them.
This is bad.
I tried butting out, but
they leave me no choice.
Time to take charge and
revive this conversation.
Listen, you two, allow me
to demonstrate a new party
trick I came up with.
You do remember last time, right?
That was rough.
I'm sorry, but if the mood gets any more
hellish, even I won't be able to help.
Right ahead.
I'd like to see it.
God, what are you going to do, Gero?
Spew liquid DIY candy out of your mouth?
Please don't ruin your
chances with an Eshinou.
Hey, this flower matches my scarf.
Oh, I love these!
I used to think all a party trick
had to do was get attention.
Just goes to show you how much I know.
But you taught me.
I got to see that actually.
The whole point is to do something
that entertains you, you know?
Mr. Kato.
I came up with a new trick
too, if you want to see.
I think you'll like it!
They might suck at
talking but if they found
a different way of
connecting with each other?
Who cares?
They had a great time.
Same here.
So I guess uh well be the best you can be.
Thanks!
I won't see you again, right?
You can tell me.
Well, my mission's complete.
You wouldn't guess, but I
actually have a greedy side.
There are tons of things I want to do.
I can't stand the thought of missing out.
I want to go to college
and run the company.
And maybe...
even fall in love, too.
Just wanted to say
thanks for the other day.
Shiori, your chariot awaits.
You know, I had a whole lot
of fun hanging out tonight.
I can't believe I almost forgot to
ask if you'd add me as a friend.
And through this, I'd
like to see you again.
I planned out 65,536 scenarios
giving him to add me!
And I still almost have
a heart attack asking!
I can't tell if Hureshi knows into me.
Or was that her just being polite?
For real.
It's a total mystery.
Either way, there's no
need to rush things.
Building any relationship takes some time.
You're right.
So then, how about we start
our next operation on Sunday?
I can't do it then. Why?
Do you have other plans?
Yeah.
A friend is getting married.
Take that, boys.
Oh, please, please, please, oh!
Take that, oh. Ah!
Ah
Ah!
keep my own a bit I will
always go on high levels I
will just keep my own a
bit I will also make a show
I feel creepy, oh, make a noise
Ah, dance the smell I feel
blessed by you, I am not a man
It's just a stand.
I'll take another chateau bridge.
Anna, I promise I'll find
your marriage. Now leave.
Next time, the Bug Master's Wedding.